

Contacts

a.bertash.dev@gmail.com

@AndrewBertash

github.com/ABertashDev

+38 096 728 37 24

Rivne, Ukraine

Skills

.NET 6, C# MS SQL Server ASP .NET Core MySQL, T-SQL **EF** Core PostgreSQL LINQ Apache Razor Pages **TeamCity**

Jira/Confluence

Blazor Server Web API

MVC

 $\bigcirc\bigcirc$ P Swagger PostMan **REST API** nUnit SOLID, GOF

Agile, Scrum, HTML/CSS other software XML/JSON development methodologies 1C Enterprise

Languages

English B1 (Intermediate) Ukrainian Native Russian Fluent

Bertash Andrii

JUNIOR .NET SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Profile

I am a software engineer with more than 6 years of commercial experience. I have organizational and problem-solving skills with a high level of self-motivation for work. I am easy and fast learn new technologies, frameworks, tools, etc.

I am an adaptable person. I have worked with different costumers. They had disparate requirements and expectations of me. I have been able to adjust my possibilities and skills to meet each of their needs.

I am good at producing quality work in a team environment. In addition, I am very comfortable with public speaking.

Seeking to apply my experience and skills to benefit your company as a .NET developer. I am tired to be unrecognized developer and it is a reason why I want to switch to .NET technologies stack and become a part of the "true developers" community

Projects

Junior .NET

Online recipe book

GitHub

01.2023 - now

Online recipe book. ASP .NET Core, Web API, EF Core, LINQ, Razor Pages, Swagger, nUnit, mySQL, HTML/CSS

Experience

1C Developer / Architect / PM / QA

03.2021 - now

Freelance projects, Rivne

Participated in many projects on the development and implementation 1C/BAS solutions for various types of businesses. Agreement work with the customers. Analysis and description of requirements. Connection trading equipment. Technical support

1C Developer / Architect / QA

08.2019 - now

ERP Data Service Ltd., Rivne

Franchisee team member. Development of solutions for automation of business processes and API integrations. Analysis and description of requirements. Connection of trading equipment

1C Developer

06.2016 - 07.2019

Renome-Smart Ltd., Rivne

Franchisee team member. Participated in many projects on the development and implementation of ERP and CRM systems based on 1C for various types of businesses. API integrations

Teacher/lecturer 05.2014 - 05.2016

GRAND (itosvita), Rivne

Teaching children according to the program, explanation of the material, checking the completion of tasks, maintaining documentation

Education

Junior .NET

EPAM University

Certificate

06.2022 - 10.2022

Successfully completed .NET Summer Program 2022

BAS: Professional HS "SAB"

Certificate Professional in the implementation of BAS solutions for business

SoftServe Academy

Course "Test automation with Python".

1C: Professional

1C Ukraine

automation

Certificate

Diploma

09.2017

03 2021

Trainee QA

09.2018 - 10.2018

Professional in using 1C: Enterprise 8.3 platform mechanisms

Bachelor's Degree 09.2013 - 07.2017

Rivne State University of the Humanities

Economic Cybernetics Bachelor's Degree (Diploma with honours)